A Guide to the Harry F. Byrd Jr. Papers
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series III: Legislative Files
  - Subseries A: General
    - Strip Mining, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 172)
    - Supreme Court, 1967-1969 (Box Box 172)
    - Supreme Court Nomination: G. Harrold Carswell, 1970 Mar-May; (4 folders) (Box Box 172)
    - Supreme Court Nomination: G. Harrold Carswell, 1970 Feb-Mar; (2 folders) (Box Box 173)
    - Supreme Court Nomination: Abe Fortas, 1968 Sep 24-Dec; (6 folders) (Box Box 173)
    - Supreme Court Nomination: Abe Fortas, 1968 Jun-Sep 23; (4 folders) (Box Box 174)
    - Supreme Court Nomination: Thurgood Marshall, 1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 174)
    - Tariff Commission, 1967-1970 (Box Box 174)
    - Tariff Legislation, 1966, 1971-1973; (3 folders) (Box Box 175)
    - Tax Legislation, 1971 Jun-1973 Jan; (4 folders) (Box Box 175)
    - Tax Legislation, 1968 Feb-1971 May; (7 folders) (Box Box 176)
    - Tax Legislation, 1967 Oct 24-1967; (7 folders) (Box Box 177)
    - Tax Legislation, 1967 Aug-Oct 23; (7 folders) (Box Box 178)
    - Tax Legislation, 1967 Mar-Aug 22; (7 folders) (Box Box 179)
    - Tax Legislation, 1966 Jan-1967 Feb; (9 folders) (Box Box 180)
    - Tax Legislation: Added Value Tax, 1970-1972 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Asset Depreciation Range, 1971 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Charitable Foundations, 1971-1972 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Credit for Educational Expenses, 1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: EPA Tax Relief, 1971-1972 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Estate Tax, 1970-1972 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Interest Equalization Tax, 1971 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Interstate Taxation Bill, 1970-1971 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Investment Credit and Sub-Chapter 5, 1971 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Long-Term Contracts Accounting, 1971-1973 (Box Box 181)
    - Tax Legislation: Military Residence, Sale of, 1971 (Box Box 182)
    - Tax Legislation: Mills-Mansfield Tax Reform, 1972 (Box Box 182)
    - Tax Legislation: Private Pension Plan, 1970-1972 (Box Box 182)
    - Tax Legislation: Revenue Act of 1971, 1971, n.d.; (5 folders) (Box Box 182)
    - Tax Legislation: Revenue Act of 1971 - Testimony (Box Box 183)
    - Tax Legislation: Revenue Act of 1972, 1971-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 183)
    - Tax Legislation: Revenue Sharing, 1970-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 183)
    - Tax Legislation: Small Business Tax Simplification & Reform, 1971 (Box Box 183)
    - Tax Legislation: Telegrams sent by Harry F. Byrd, Jr., 1966 (Box Box 183)
    - Tax Legislation: Trade Bill, 1970-1971 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Accumulation and Multiple Trusts, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Adjustment Tax Burden For Individuals, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Capital Gains & Losses, 1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Charitable Contributions, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Cooperatives, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Deferred Income, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Depreciation by Regulated Industries, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Farm Losses, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Financial Institutions, 1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Investment Tax Credit, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Multiple Corporations, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Natural Resources, 1969 (Box Box 184)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Oil Depletion, 1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Private Foundations, 1969; (3 folders) (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Real Estate Depreciation, 1969 (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Restricted Stock Plans, 1969 (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: State and Municipal Bonds, 1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Stock Dividends, 1969 (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Sub-Chapters and Corporations, 1969 (Box Box 185)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Table of Contents & Summary, 1969 (Box Box 186)
    - Tax Reform Bill: Tax Exempt Organizations, 1969; (4 folders) (Box Box 186)
    - Taxes: Internal Revenue Service and Chapa Arlington Cars, 1967-1969 (Box Box 186)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1968-1971 (Box Box 186)
    - Transportation Department, 1971 Nov-1973; (7 folders) (Box Box 187)
    - Transportation Department, 1971 Mar-Oct; (8 folders) (Box Box 188)
    - Transportation Department, 1968-1971 Feb; (8 folders) (Box Box 189)
    - Transportation Department, 1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 190)
    - Treasury Department, 1969-1973; (4 folders) (Box Box 190)
    - Treasury Department, 1966-1968; (3 folders) (Box Box 191)
    - Unemployment Compensation Bills, 1966, 1970-1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 191)
    - United Nations, 1967-1968, 1972 (Box Box 191)
    - United States Chamber of Commerce, 1967 (Box Box 191)
    - United States Information Agency, 1967-1970 (Box Box 191)
    - Veterans Administration, 1969-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 191)
    - Veteran's Administration, 1966-1968; (2 folders) (Box Box 192)
    - Veteran's Administration: G.I. Loans, 1966-1967 (Box Box 192)
    - Veteran's Administration: Life Article, 1970 (Box Box 192)
    - Veteran's Administration: Real Estate Attorney Fees, 1972 (Box Box 192)
    - Veterans Legislation, 1972 Mar-Dec; (4 folders) (Box Box 192)
    - Veterans Legislation, 1967 Sep-1972 Feb; (7 folders) (Box Box 193)
    - Veterans Legislation, 1966 Apr-1967 Aug; (8 folders) (Box Box 194)
    - Veterans Legislation, 1966 Jan-Mar (Box Box 195)
    - Vietnam, 1967 Oct 9-1972; (8 folders) (Box Box 195)
    - Vietnam, 1967 Sep 13-Oct 6; (7 folders) (Box Box 196)
    - Vietnam, 1967 Mar-Sep 12; (8 folders) (Box Box 197)
    - Vietnam, 1966 Feb-Oct; (7 folders) (Box Box 198)
    - Vietnam, 1965-1966 Jan; (2 folders) (Box Box 199)
    - Vietnam Condolences, 1967-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 199)
    - Vietnam: Free World Shipping, 1967-1969 (Box Box 199)
    - Vietnam: Prisoners of War, 1970-1972 (Box Box 199)
    - Virginia, 1972-1973; (6 folders) (Box Box 200)
    - Virginia, 1971 May-Dec; (9 folders) (Box Box 201)
    - Virginia, 1970 Jul-1971 Apr; (8 folders) (Box Box 202)
    - Virginia, 1970 Jan-Jun; (7 folders) (Box Box 203)
    - Virginia, 1969 Apr-Dec; (7 folders) (Box Box 204)
    - Virginia, 1966 Dec-1969 Mar; (7 folders) (Box Box 205)
    - Virginia, 1966 Apr 13-Nov; (7 folders) (Box Box 206)
    - Virginia, 1965 Nov-1966 Apr 12; (5 folders) (Box Box 207)
    - Virginia: Air Pollution, 1968 (Box Box 207)
    - Virginia: Alcoholic Beverages Control Board, 1966-1969 (Box Box 207)
    - Virginia: City Planning, Zoning, etc., 1967 (Box Box 207)
    - Virginia: Commercial Fishing, 1970 (Box Box 207)
    - Virginia: Commission of Game and Inland Fisheries, 1966-1972 (Box Box 208)
    - Virginia: Conservation and Economic Development Commission, 1966-1968 (Box Box 208)
    - Virginia: Convention Arrangements, 1967 (Box Box 208)
    - Virginia: Division of Motor Vehicles, 1965-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 208)
    - Virginia: Education, 1967-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 208)
    - Virginia Employment Commission, 1967-1968 (Box Box 209)
    - Virginia: Fairfax County Sewage Problems, 1970-1971 (Box Box 209)
    - Virginia: Health, 1967-1968 (Box Box 209)
    - Virginia: Highways, Dept. of, 1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 209)
    - Virginia: Highways, Dept. of, 1969-1971; (6 folders) (Box Box 210)
    - Virginia: Highways, Dept. of, 1965-1968; (8 folders) (Box Box 211)
    - Virginia: History and Historical Organizations, 1966-1967 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Industrial Development, Division of, 1963, 1967 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Industry, Economy, & Manufacturing, 1967 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Judicial Matters, 1966-1967 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Laws re Voting, Residency, Taxes, etc., 1967 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Legal Aid Society of the Roanoke Valley, 1967 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: National Guard, 1967-1968 (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Norfolk Reduction-in-Force and Wages, 1971-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 212)
    - Virginia: Norfolk Reduction-in-Force and Wages, 1970; (4 folders) (Box Box 213)
    - Virginia: Norfolk Public Health Service Hospital, 1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 213)
    - Virginia: Northern Virginia Regional Park Authority, 1972 (Box Box 213)
    - Virginia: Postmaster Nominations, 1964-1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 214)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 1, 1959-1970; (2 folders) (Box Box 214)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 2, 1959-1972 (Box Box 214)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 3, 1961-1968 (Box Box 214)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 4, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 214)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 4, 1958-1969 (Box Box 215)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 5, 1961-1971; (4 folders) (Box Box 215)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 6, 1964-1971; (3 folders) (Box Box 215)
    - Virginia: Post Offices - District 6, 1958-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 216)
    - Virginia: Potomac River Basin, 1961-1970; (3 folders) (Box Box 217)
    - Virginia: Recreation, 1967 (Box Box 217)
    - Virginia: Regional Planning Commission, 1969, 1972 (Box Box 217)
    - Virginia: School Boards, 1967 (Box Box 217)
    - Virginia: State Board of Elections, 1967-1969 (Box Box 217)
    - Virginia: State Corporation Commission, 1968-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 217)
    - Virginia: State Corporation Commission, 1965-1967 (Box Box 218)
    - Virginia: Taxation, Dept. of, 1965-1970; (2 folders) (Box Box 218)
    - Virginia: Verona Dam Project, 1969 (Box Box 218)
    - Virginia: Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, 1969-1973 (Box Box 218)
    - Virginia: Voting, 1968-1972 (Box Box 218)
    - Virginia: Welfare, Dept. of, 1967-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 218)
    - Voting Record of Senator Byrd, 1972 (Box Box 218)
    - Welfare, 1969-1973; (7 folders) (Box Box 219)
    - Welfare, 1965-1966; (2 folders) (Box Box 220)
    - Welfare: Child Development & Child Care, 1968-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 220)
    - Welfare: Child Development and Child Care - Testimony, 1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 220)
    - Welfare: Family Planning, 1973 (Box Box 220)
    - Welfare: Medicare, 1973 May-Dec; (2 folders) (Box Box 220)
    - Welfare: Medicare, 1964-1973 Apr; (4 folders) (Box Box 221)
    - Welfare: National Health Care, 1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 221)
    - Welfare: Nixon Speech Rebuttal by Harry F. Byrd, Jr., 1971 (Box Box 221)
    - Welfare: Nursing Homes, 1973 (Box Box 221)
    - Welfare: Social Security, 1972 Jun-1973 Dec; (9 folders) (Box Box 222)
    - Welfare: Social Security, 1970 Jun-1972 May; (7 folders) (Box Box 223)
    - Welfare: Vocational Rehabilitation, 1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 224)
    - West Germany, 1966 (Box Box 224)
    - Wilderness Bills, 1971-1972 (Box Box 224)
    - Womens' Organizations in the United States, 1971; (3 folders) (Box Box 224)
    - World of Work Orientation Program, 1968 (Box Box 224)
  - Subseries B: Senate Committees
    - Agriculture and Forestry Committee, 1967-1968, 1971 (Box Box 225)
    - Armed Services Committee, 1969-1972; (6 folders) (Box Box 225)
    - Armed Services Committee, 1966-1968, n.d.; (4 folders) (Box Box 226)
    - Finance Committee, 1965-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 226)
- Series IV: Correspondence
  - Agnew, Spiro T., 1968-1972 (Box Box 227)
  - Battle, John S., 1968-1970 (Box Box 227)
  - Button, Robert Y., 1965-1969 (Box Box 227)
  - Byrd Business, 1967 Oct-1969; (5 folders) (Box Box 227)
  - Byrd Business, 1966-1967 Sep; (8 folders) (Box Box 228)
  - Byrd Business, 1965 (Box Box 229)
  - Byrd Business - Newspapers, 1966-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 229)
  - Byrd Family, 1966 Jun-1969; (4 folders) (Box Box 229)
  - Byrd Family, 1965 -1966 May (Box Box 230)
  - Daniel, W.C. "Dan", 1966-1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 230)
  - Fenwick, Charles R., 1966-1969 (Box Box 230)
  - Fletcher, James W., 1966-1968 (Box Box 230)
  - Gnadt, Charlton, 1965-1967, 1969; (3 folders) (Box Box 230)
  - Godwin, Mills E., Jr., 1965-1966, 1969-1970; (2 folders) (Box Box 230)
  - Harrison, Albertis, Jr., 1965-1971 (Box Box 231)
  - Harrison, Burr P., 1966-1967 (Box Box 231)
  - Hatch, Alden, 1967-1968 (Box Box 231)
  - Holton, Linwood, Jr., 1969-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 231)
  - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1966-1968 (Box Box 231)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965-1969; (3 folders) (Box Box 231)
  - Jones, Audrey, 1966-1973 (Box Box 231)
  - Kellam, Sidney S., 1966-1967 (Box Box 231)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1972 (Box Box 231)
  - re the 1967 Election (Box Box 231)
  - Nixon, Richard M., 1968-1973; (5 folders) (Box Box 232)
  - Personal, 1968 Sep-1969 Dec; (7 folders) (Box Box 233)
  - Personal, 1967 Mar-1968 Aug; (7 folders) (Box Box 234)
  - Personal, 1965 Nov-1967 Feb; (7 folders) (Box Box 235)
  - Political, 1968 Jun-1970 Mar; (7 folders) (Box Box 236)
  - Pollard, Fred G., 1966-1969 (Box Box 236)
  - Rettgers, Forrest I., 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 237)
  - Senators and Congressmen, 1971 Jun-1972 Dec; (4 folders) (Box Box 237)
  - Senators and Congressmen, 1967 Oct-1971 May; (6 folders) (Box Box 238)
  - Senators and Congressmen, 1966-1967 Sep; (3 folders) (Box Box 239)
  - Spong, William B., Jr., 1966-1973 (Box Box 239)
  - Tuck, William M., 1968-1972 (Box Box 239)
  - Utz, William Nelson, 1968-1972 (Box Box 239)
- Series V: Miscellaneous & Topical
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1971 Dec-1972 Dec; (4 folders) (Box Box 240)
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1970 Oct-1971 Nov; (5 folders) (Box Box 241)
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1970 Jan-Aug; (4 folders) (Box Box 242)
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1969; (4 folders) (Box Box 243)
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1967 Oct-1968 Dec; (4 folders) (Box Box 244)
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1966 Nov-1967 Sep; (4 folders) (Box Box 245)
  - Acceptances of Invitations to Speak, 1965 Nov-1966 Oct; (6 folders) (Box Box 246)
  - Alfalfa Club, 1965-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 247)
  - Alibi Club, 1972 (Box Box 247)
  - Apple Blossom Festival, 1966-1972; (3 folders) (Box Box 247)
  - Appointments, 1966 (Box Box 247)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1972-1973; (2 folders) (Box Box 247)
  - Bicentennial Commission, 1968-1971; (2 folders) (Box Box 248)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Cities, 1972 (Box Box 248)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Parks, 1972 (Box Box 248)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Bicentennial Parks Feasibility Study, 1972 (Box Box 248)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Budget, 1972 (Box Box 248)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box Box 249)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Exposition, 1970-1972 (Box Box 249)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Heritage '76 Committee, 1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 249)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Legislation, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 249)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Memoranda, 1972-1973 (Box Box 249)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Minutes of Meetings, 1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 250)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box Box 250)
  - Bicentennial Commission: National Historic Records Program, 1972 (Box Box 250)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Organization & Staffing, 1972 (Box Box 250)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Printed, 1972-1973 (Box Box 250)
  - Bicentennial Commission: Proposals & Reports, 1972 (Box Box 250)
  - Congressional Record Inserts, 1966-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 251)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1967-1969 (Box Box 251)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1968 Jul-Nov; (2 folders) (Box Box 251)
  - Democratic National Convention, 1968 Mar-Jun; (2 folders) (Box Box 252)
  - Democratic State Central Committee, 1967-1970 (Box Box 252)
  - Family Tree, 1962 & 1970 (Box Box 252)
  - Form Letters, 1966-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 252)
  - Governorship of Virginia, 1968 (Box Box 252)
  - Greetings Sample, 1965-1966, 1968-1969; (2 folders) (Box Box 252)
  - Hall of Fame, 1968-1969 (Box Box 252)
  - Jefferson-Jackson Day Dinners, 1965-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 253)
  - Lewis, the Rev. Cotesworth Pinckney-Lyndon Johnson Controversy, 1967-1968 (Box Box 253)
  - Luncheons in the Senate Dining Room, 1966 (Box Box 253)
  - Media, 1972 Jan-1973 Jan; (5 folders) (Box Box 253)
  - Media, 1969 Jul-1971 Dec; (8 folders) (Box Box 254)
  - Media, 1967 Oct-1969 Jun; (7 folders) (Box Box 255)
  - Media, 1966 Jul-1967 Sep; (6 folders) (Box Box 256)
  - Media, 1964-1966 Jun; (2 folders) (Box Box 257)
  - Newsclippings re Politicians, 1968-1972 (Box Box 257)
  - Office Memoranda, 1969-1972 (Box Box 257)
  - Speaker Requests, 1971-1972; (2 folders) (Box Box 257)
  - Special Committees, 1970-1972; (4 folders) (Box Box 257)
  - Special Committees, 1965-1969; (6 folders) (Box Box 258)
  - Tax Foundation, 1966-1973; (6 folders) (Box Box 259)
  - Trips: Asia, 1967; (3 folders) (Box Box 259)
  - Trips: Central America, 1967 (Box Box 259)
  - Trips: Middle East, 1967-1968 (Box Box 259)
- Series VI: Chronological Consituent & Fan Mail (Sampled)
  - Constituent Mail, 1965 Nov-1967 Mar; (6 folders) (Box Box 260)
  - Constituent Mail, 1967 Apr-Dec; (7 folders) (Box Box 261)
  - Constituent Mail, 1968-1969, 1971 Jan-Mar; (4 folders) (Box Box 262)
  - Constituent Mail, 1971 Apr-Dec; (6 folders) (Box Box 263)
  - Constituent Mail, 1972 Jan-1973 Jan; (7 folders) (Box Box 264)
  - Fan Mail, 1967-1969 Jun; (5 folders) (Box Box 265)
  - Fan Mail, 1969 Jul-1972; (5 folders) (Box Box 266)
- Daily Carbons 1965-1972 (Box 1-30)
  - "A" - "M" 1965 Dec. [1] - 1966 Apr. 11 (Box 1)
  - "N" - "Z" 1965 Dec. [1] - 1966 Apr. 11 (Box 2)
  - "A" - "G" 1966 Apr. [11] - 1966 July 17 (Box 2)
  - "H" - "Z" 1966 Apr. [11] - 1966 July 17 (Box 3)
  - "A" - "O" 1966 July 18 - 1966 Nov. 8 (Box 4)
  - "P" - "Z" 1966 July 18 - 1966 Nov. 8 (Box 5)
  - "A" - "Ha" 1966 Nov. 6 - 1967 Feb. 16 (Box 5)
  - "He" - "Z" 1966 Nov. 6 - 1967 Feb. 16 (Box 6)
  - "A" - "O" 1967 Feb. 17 - 1967 June 12 (Box 7)
  - "P" - "Z" 1967 Feb. 17 - 1967 June 12 (Box 8)
  - "A" - "G" 1967 Jun [13] - 1967 Oct. [12] (Box 8)
  - "H" - "Z" 1967 June [13] - 1967 Oct. [12] (Box 9)
  - "A" - "M" 1967 Oct. [13] - 1968 Mar. [12] (Box 10)
  - "N" - "Z" 1967 Oct. [13] - 1968 Mar. [12] (Box 11)
  - "A" - "F" 1968 Mar. [13] - 1968 July [12] (Box 11)
  - "G" - "V" 1968 Mar. [13] - 1968 July [12] (Box 12)
  - "W" - "Z" 1968 Mar. [13] - 1968 July [12] (Box 13)
  - "A" - "L" 1968 July [13] - 1969 Feb. [12] (Box 13)
  - "M" - "Z" 1968 July [13] - 1969 Feb. [12] (Box 14)
  - "A" - "D" 1969 Feb. [13] - 1969 June [12] (Box 14)
  - "E" - "Z" 1969 Feb. [13] - 1969 June [12] (Box 15)
  - "A" - "M" 1969 June 11 - 1969 Nov. 12 (Box 16)
  - "N" - "Z" 1969 June 11 - 1969 Nov. 12 (Box 17)
  - "A" - "D" 1969 Nov. [13] - 1970 Mar. 23 (Box 17)
  - "E" - "S" 1969 Nov. [13] - 1970 Mar. 23 (Box 18)
  - "T" - "Z" 1969 Nov. [13] - 1970 Mar. 23 (Box 19)
  - "A" - "J" 1970 Mar. 26 - 1970 July 6 (Box 19)
  - "K" - "Z" 1969 Nov. [13] - 1970 Mar. 23 (Box 20)
  - "A" - "Mc" 1970 July 8 - 1970 Oct. 20 (Box 21)
  - "Me" - "Z" 1970 July 8 - 1970 Oct. 20 (Box 22)
  - "A" - "C" 1970 Oct. 21 - 1971 Feb. 9 (Box 22)
  - "D" - "R" 1970 Oct. 21 - 1971 Feb. 9 (Box 23)
  - "S" - "Z" 1970 Oct. 21 - 1971 Feb. 9 (Box 24)
  - "A" - "H" 1971 Feb. 10 - 1971 May 28 (Box 24)
  - "I" - "Z" 1971 Feb. 10 - 1971 May 28 (Box 25)
  - "A" - "M" 1971 June 1 - 1971 Oct. 30 (Box 26)
  - "N" - "Z" 1971 June 1 - 1971 Oct. 30 (Box 27)
  - "Mi" - "Z" 1971 Nov. [1] - 1972 Mar. [31] (Box 27)
  - "A" - "Q" 1972 Apr. 4 - 1972 July 31 (Box 28)
  - "P" - "Z" 1972 Apr. 4 - 1972 July 31 (Box 29)
  - "A" - "H" 1972 Aug. 1 - 1972 Dec. 31 (Box 29)
  - "I" - "Z" 1972 Aug. 1 - 1972 Dec. 31 (Box 30)
- Audiotape
  - William McHenry sings "Blue Ridge Lullaby" at the Luray Singing Towers, 1968 Aug 4; T-904
  - Remarks of Harry F. Byrd, Jr., upon arrival at Taipei airport, 1967 [Apr]; T-904
- Oversize Folder
  - Campaign Poster for Election to the U.S. Senate that says, "Byrd Working For You U.S. Senate", 1966 (Box Oversize)
  - Senate Resolution 317, expressing condolences of the Senate upon the death of Senator Byrd's father, Harry F. Byrd, Sr., 1966 Nov (Box Oversize)
  - County of Los Angeles Board of Supervisors Resolution passed in memory of Harry F. Byrd, Sr., 1966 Dec (Box Oversize)
  - Virginia State Board of Elections Certificate signifying Harry F. Byrd, Jr.'s election as an United States Senator representing Virginia, 1970 (Box Oversize)
  - Photograph of Byrd and others in a meeting at the White House, used in the October 1970 Newsletter (Box Oversize)